{
    "subject": "resource/Pennsylvania",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "resource/List_of_U.S._states_by_date_of_admission_to_the_Union",
    "human_readable": "The title of Pennsylvania is 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.789869487285614,
            "question": "What does 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7824570536613464,
            "question": "What information can be found in a list of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7658032178878784,
            "question": "What category does the title 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7505908608436584,
            "question": "What is the title of Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6787353157997131,
            "question": "Can you provide an example of a state that joined the Union before Pennsylvania?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6177025437355042,
            "question": "Is Pennsylvania a state in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4699382781982422,
            "question": "When did Pennsylvania become a state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35876184701919556,
            "question": "How might knowing the date of admission to the Union be useful for understanding American history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34256961941719055,
            "question": "Are there other lists that categorize U.S. states?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24420586228370667,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of the order in which states joined the Union?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of Pennsylvania is 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7938_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other lists that categorize U.S. states?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7938_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might knowing the date of admission to the Union be useful for understanding American history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7938_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Pennsylvania become a state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7938_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7938_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have more queries!  I'm ready to analyze them."
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents contain detailed lists and information about the order of state admissions to the United States, including Pennsylvania's admission on December 12, 1787. The title 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union' seems accurate based on the content provided in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7938/re-ranker-msmarco/33.txt"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe query \"The title of Pennsylvania is 'List of U.S. states by date of admission to the Union'.\" can be considered correct according to the documents provided, as the information about statehood and admission dates for various states, including a mention of Pennsylvania's admission on December 12, 1787, aligns with this title."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text clearly states \"This is a list of US states by date of statehood, that is, the date when each US state joined the Union.\" and it repeatedly mentions \"date of admission to the Union\" throughout.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}